# Suprabha

Btm 2nd Stage Bangalore, 560076

M 8148606370

suprabha.me blog.suprabha.me

## SUMMARY

Creative Front-end Developer with 2+ years of experience leveraging JavaScript to build responsive websites, mobile apps, and interactive features that drive business growth and improve UX.

I love to implement designs in pixel perfect than stand back and adore it. Design is not just work for me, it's the way I see the world.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer, **Zoomcar.com**

Bangalore — October 2018 - Present

As a Frontend Developer, I am responsible for zoomcar.com funnel.

#### **Accomplishments**

- Creating search widget in Web Components across all platforms.
- Integrating zoomcar PWA with B2B partner i.e. Phonepe, Ixigo, Flipkart.
- Executed major sale changes in tight timeline.

# Associate Software Engineer, Zoomcar.com

Bangalore — October 2016 - October 2018

As a Frontend Developer, I am responsible for web and admin.

## **EDUCATION**

Hindustan University Chennai B.tech IT, 2015

Regional Secondary School Intermediate in Science 2009-11

## **LANGUAGES**

JavaScript(ES6), HTML5, CSS3(SCSS), GraphQL

# FRAMEWORK AND LIBRARIES

Vue.js, React Native, React, Redux, Native Base, Web Components, Bootstrap, Materialize CSS, jQuery, Wordpress, Angular Material, D3.js

# **TOOLS AND API**

Photoshop, Illustrator, Git, npm, webpack, SVG, Zeplin, Invision, Sketch

# **ACHIEVEMENT**

Top achiever in my batch 2015.

#### **Accomplishments**

- Working on PEDL (zoomcar's bicycle sharing platform). Build and managed multiple pages across project.
- Developed PEDL's landing page (pedl.zoomcar.com)
- Took ownership of career page built resume uploading feature using AWS lambda and 3rd party API.
- Improved SEO of website which resulted in 40% increase in organic traffic.
- Built solution for PEDL host program using Lambda function and dynamoDB which resulted in high level of engagement for PEDL host program.
- Took end to end ownership of number of Internal Dashboard projects some of which includes but not limited to are dynamic pricing dashboard, one-way dashboard, retention dashboard. Dashboard were build using ROR and HAML.
- Built templates for dynamically generated marketing, airport, taxi, cab pages. Which is being used for generating more than 1400+ page.
- Developed lot of landing pages for different campaigns.

#### *UI Developer*, affluenze.co.in

Bangalore — April 2016 - September 2016

As a UI developer at affluenze.co.in my responsibility was to take care of frontend website which includes designing changes and performance optimization.

#### **Accomplishments**

- Built a system which allows the faculty to create, modify and store all the information of students and questions.
- Student can able to give online exam and the faculty can take the attendance online itself.
- Build the full website which will be helpful for students. Student can easily get the all previous question paper and can prepare for the exam.

Member of Hindustan Google Student Ambassador Program 2014.

Participated in ACM ICPC 2013.

# PROJECTS (Github)

# Software Inventory Management, B.Tech final year project

 ${\it Role-Architect,\,Developer}$ 

Optimize our processes for ordering, storing, and tracking inventory of software.

- Build it using JSP, Javascript, Java and MySQL.
- Used Tomcat server.

## Fooodie App

 ${\rm Role-UI/UX\ Developer}$ 

- Designed UX flow.
- Built it using React Native and redux.
- Created both Client and Admin app.
- Used EXPO and Native Base for fast implementation.
- Built many features such as push notification and map integration .

#### Hobber Ecommerce Website

Role — UI/UX Developer

It is an Ecommerce website for

- Built it using Vue.js.
- API integration with Magento.